Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files A
    - Anderson, Samuel .E (Box A-5, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: Orie Damewood, George Jervas
    - Anerson, Satchel (Box A-5, Folder 151)
    - Anderson, Savannah (Box A-5, Folder 152)
    - Anderson, Sharon (Box A-5, Folder 153)
    - Anderson, Sheila (Box A-5, Folder 154)
      Also one velox print. One print has two staples in border.
      Photographer if identified: Billly Pierce Jr
    - Anderson, Shirley (Box A-5, Folder 155)
      Two typescript leaves attached to print with staple.
    - Anderson, Sidney P. (Box A-5, Folder 156)
      One negative strip containing one image.
    - Anderson, Stella (Box A-5, Folder 157)
    - Anderson, Stell (Box A-5, Folder 158)
    - Anderson, Subbeal (Dr.) (Box A-5, Folder 159)
    - Anderson, ("Sugarfoot") (Box A-5, Folder 160)
    - Anderson, W.T (Box A-5, Folder 161)
      Also two paper stereotype matrices and one typescript leaf.
    - Anderson, Walter (Box A-5, Folder 162)
    - Anderson, Webester (General) (Box A-5, Folder 163)
    - Anderson, Wendell W. (Box A-5, Folder 164)
    - Anderson, Wendy M (Box A-5, Folder 165)
    - Anderson, William (Box A-5, Folder 166)
    - Anderson, William (Box A-5, Folder 167)
    - Anderson, William (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-5, Folder 168)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Versatile Photography
    - Anderson, William G. (Dr.) (Box A-5, Folder 169)
    - Anderson, Willie Joe (Box A-5, Folder 170)
      One paper stereotype matrix, with a typescript leaf attached by paperclip.
    - Anderson, Willam R. (Mrs.) (Box A-5, Folder 171)
      Photographer if identified: Dumelle
    - Anderson, Wilton (Box A-5, Folder 172)
    - Andrade, Lori Marie (Box A-5, Folder 173)
    - Andrade, Rebecca D. (Box A-5, Folder 174)
    - Andre, Braillon (Box A-5, Folder 175)
      One computer-printed typescript taped to verso of print.
    - Andre, Francois (Box A-5, Folder 176)
    - Andre, Henry (Box A-5, Folder 177)
    - Andre, Renee (Box A-5, Folder 178)
      Nine negative slides containing 19 images.
    - Andre, Cisco (Box A-5, Folder 179)
      Photographer if identified: Harry H. Adams
    - Anderson, Sylvester (Box A-5, Folder 180)
    - Anderson, T. (Box A-5, Folder 181)
    - Andrerson, Thelma (Box A-5, Folder 182)
    - Anderson, Thomas (Box A-5, Folder 183)
    - Anderson, Tommy (Box A-5, Folder 184)
      Two negative slides containing two images.
    - Anderson, Toyce (Box A-5, Folder 185)
      Ms. paragraph written on verso of print.
    - Anderson, Ulysses (Box A-5, Folder 186)
    - Anderson, Vera (Box A-5, Folder 187)
    - Anderson Virgil (Box A-5, Folder 188)
    - Anderson, Vivian (Box A-5, Folder 189)
    - Anderson, W.A (Box A-5, Folder 190)
    - Andrews, Alan (Box A-5, Folder 191)
    - Andrews, Avis (Box A-5, Folder 192)
      One computer-printed typescript leaf taped to verso of print.
      Photographer if identified: Blanche
    - Andrews, Benjamin L. (Box A-5, Folder 193)
    - Andrews, Benny (Box A-5, Folder 194)
      Photographer if identified: Lender - Heller Gallery
    - Andrews, B. (P&G) (Box A-5, Folder 195)
      Also one typescript leaf.
    - Andrews, Bert (Box A-5, Folder 196)
    - Andrews, Bert (Box A-5, Folder 197)
      Photographer if identified: McLaren-Anderson Associates
    - Andrews, Carl (Box A-5, Folder 198)
    - Andrews, Carl (Box A-5, Folder 199)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Brown
    - Andrews, Curtis E (Box A-5, Folder 200)
    - Andrews, Daniel (Box A-5, Folder 201)
      Photographer if identified: Foto Estudio
    - Andrews, W. Daniel (Box A-5, Folder 202)
    - Andrews, Debbie (Box A-5, Folder 203)
    - Andrews, D. W (Box A-5, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Polks Studio
    - Andrews, David R. (Box A-5, Folder 205)
    - Andrews, Elise (Box A-5, Folder 206)
      One print has two ms. leaves attached with paperclip to print. Also one loose ms. leaf, one bundle of 2 ms. and 2 typescript leaves (attached with a paperclip to 2 prints), one paper stereotype matrix, and seven negative slides containing ten images.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Nichols, A. Hansen, Dummett, James Gilbert
    - Andrews, Elise (Box A-5, Folder 207)
    - Andrews, Ernestyne (Box A-5, Folder 208)
      Photographer if identified: Larry Andrews, Bro. David McAdams
    - Addrews, Ernie (Box A-5, Folder 209)
    - Andrews, Frieda Louise, Mrs. (Box A-5, Folder 210)
      Also 3 three paper stereotype matrices and one typescript leaf.
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Rapid News Photo
    - Andrews, Frieda (Box A-5, Folder 211)
    - Andrews, G.K. (Dr.) (Box A-5, Folder 212)
    - Andrews, George (Box A-5, Folder 213)
    - Andrews, Helen (Box A-5, Folder 214)
    - Andrews, Emmanule (Box A-5, Folder 215)
    - Andrews, Inex (Box A-5, Folder 216)
    - Andrews, Ismay (Box A-5, Folder 217)
    - Andrews, Ivan (Box A-5, Folder 218)
      Photographer if identified: Pope Studio
    - Andrews, Jean (Miss) (Box A-5, Folder 219)
    - Andrews, Jennifer (Box A-5, Folder 220)
    - Andrews, Julie (Box A-5, Folder 221)
    - Andrew, Henry (Box A-5, Folder 222)
      Photographer if identified: Leonard Bass
    - Andrews, H. Henry (Box A-5, Folder 223)
    - Andrews, Kim (Box A-5, Folder 224)
    - Andrews, Louis. B (ATTY.) (Box A-5, Folder 225)
    - Andrews, Mildred (Mrs.) (Box A-5, Folder 226)
      One print has staple in border. One print is taped to a loose leaf.
    - Andrews, Miriam (Box A-5, Folder 227)
    - Andrews, Olga (Box A-5, Folder 228)
    - Andrews, (Paul Vs. Harold J) (Box A-5, Folder 229)
    - Andrews, Regina (Box A-5, Folder 230)
      Photographer if identified: Fred Stien
    - Anderson, Robert (Box A-5, Folder 231)
    - Andrews, Rosa (Box A-5, Folder 232)
      One ms. leaf stapled to recto of print
    - Andrews, Ruby (Box A-5, Folder 233)
    - Andrew, Thomas (Box A-5, Folder 234)
      One typescript leaf attached to verso of print.
    - Andrews, Tina (Box A-5, Folder 235)
    - Andrews, Vivan L. (Box A-5, Folder 236)
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick
    - Andrews, Williams T. (Box A-5, Folder 237)
      One computer-printed typescript clipping taped to verso of print.
      Photographer if identified: Blackstone-Shelburne
    - And the Echoes (Box A-5, Folder 238)
    - Angola (Box A-5, Folder 239)
    - Andrews WM. T. (Assemblyman) Anderson, Regina (Box A-5, Folder 240)
      Photographer if identified: M. Smith, Rapid News Photo
    - Andrews, Yvonne (Box A-5, Folder 241)
      Photographer if identified: Oscar Mallory
    - Anduze, Carl L. (Box A-5, Folder 242)
    - Anduze, Roy (Dr. & Mrs) (Box A-5, Folder 243)
    - Anduze, Roy (Mrs.) (Box A-5, Folder 244)
    - Anduze, Vivian (Scott, John. Mrs) (Box A-5, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: Claude Maloon
    - Andy + Bey (Sister) (Box A-5, Folder 246)
    - Andy and Adele (Box A-5, Folder 247)
    - Angels, Guardian (Box A-5, Folder 248)
    - Angelo, Maya (Box A-5, Folder 249)
    - Anekawe, Cecilia N. (Box A-5, Folder 250)
    - Anfield, Marvin "Duke" (Box A-5, Folder 251)
    - Angelique, (And the Third World) (Box A-5, Folder 252)
    - Angelo, Georgio Sant (Box A-5, Folder 253)
    - Anheuser - Busch, (Inc) (Box A-5, Folder 254)
      One torn typescript leaf.
    - Agnell, Chas B. (Box A-5, Folder 255)
      Photographer if identified: Cronhardt & Sons
    - Angellus, Frederick (Box A-5, Folder 256)
    - Angela and ' Rene (Box A-5, Folder 257)
    - Angelou, Maya (Box A-5, Folder 258)
    - Anglada, Mario (Box A-5, Folder 259)
    - Anglia, Granville (Box A-5, Folder 260)
    - Anglini, Disraeli L (Box A-5, Folder 261)
    - Angola (Box A-5, Folder 262)
    - Angelou, Maya (Box A-5, Folder 263)
    - Animals (Part 1) (Box A-5, Folder 264)
      12 prints have typescript leaves adhered to verso of print. One print has three typescript leaves attached with a paperclip on. One print has a typescript leaf attached by staple. Also 4 loose typescript leaves and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, New York Zoological Society Photo,United Press International Photo,Fair Weather Photo, Nichols, M & M Smith Photo, International News Photo, Skippy Etheridge, Parks Admin, Rapid News Photo
    - Animals (Part 2) (Box A-5, Folder 265)
      Note on folder: "Continued."
    - Animals (Part 3) (Box A-5, Folder 266)
    - Anita and Y (Box A-5, Folder 267)
    - Anker, Irving (Box A-5, Folder 268)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, John Kane
    - Ankinwade, Henry (Box A-5, Folder 269)
    - Ankarah, Joseph (Box A-5, Folder 270)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photo
    - Anmons, Richard (Box A-5, Folder 271)
    - Anniversary Celebrations (Box A-5, Folder 272)
      One ms. paragraph written on verso of print. Also one velox print
      Photographer if identified: Herbert Hawkins, Harris Photo, James Gilbert, James Samuels,
    - Another World (Box A-5, Folder 273)
    - Ansah, Kwaw (Box A-5, Folder 274)
    - Ansley, Terry (Box A-5, Folder 275)
    - Ansley, William (Box A-5, Folder 276)
    - Anthony, Bill J. (Box A-5, Folder 277)
    - Anthony, Boyce Chadwick (Mrs.& Mrs.0 (Box A-5, Folder 278)
      Photographer if identified: Official U.S. Air Force Photography
    - Anthony, Charles (Box A-5, Folder 279)
      Photographer if identified: Standard Studios
    - Anthony, Earl (Box A-5, Folder 280)
    - Anthony, Edwards (Box A-5, Folder 281)
    - Anthony, Frederick (Box A-5, Folder 282)
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Yearwood
    - Anthony, George (Dr. &Mrs.) (Box A-5, Folder 283)
    - Anthony, H. (Dr.) (Box A-5, Folder 284)
    - Anthony, Henry (Box A-5, Folder 285)
    - Anthony, Irving (Rev.) (Box A-5, Folder 286)
    - Anthony, Joseph Jan (Box A-5, Folder 287)
    - Anthony, Jean (Box A-5, Folder 288)
    - Anthony, Michael (Father) (Box A-5, Folder 289)
    - Anthony, Reva (Box A-5, Folder 290)
    - Anthony, Toni (Box A-5, Folder 291)
      Photographer if identified: Jimmy Sunshine
    - Anthony, Tony (Box A-5, Folder 292)
    - Anthony, Sterling Jr (Box A-5, Folder 293)
      One computer-printed typescript leaf stapled to recto of print.
    - Anthony, Vere (Box A-6, Folder 1)
    - Anti Khomeni Demo (Box A-6, Folder 2)
    - Anti War (Persian Gulf) (Box A-6, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: Robert L. Haggins, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Stu Lewis, Curt Clemons Foto, A. Frazier
    - "Antigone" (Box A-6, Folder 4)
    - Antioch Baptist Church (Box A-6, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Dummett, Gill Photographers
    - Anton, Sharon (Box A-6, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: Grace Del Marco Agency
    - Antrum, James (Box A-6, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Office of Information Services South Carolina State College
    - Apartheid (Box A-6, Folder 8)
      Folder title is "Against Apartheid."
    - Apartheid (Box A-6, Folder 9)
      Photographer if identified: Janet Griffith, Michael J. Henry, Peterkin Photo, George Cohen
    - Apartheid (Box A-6, Folder 10)
      Folder title is "Anti-Apartheid Warmup."
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Kwame Brathwaite, Curt Clemons
    - Apartheid Boycott + Protests (Box A-6, Folder 11)
      Photographer if identified: Bruce Williams, George Cohen, Pictorial Enterprise, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Beuford Smith/Cesaire
    - Apollo 11 (Box A-6, Folder 12)
      Four prints have typescript leaves affixed to verso. Also contains two press releases.
      Photographer if identified: NASA, United Press International Photo
    - Apollo 15 (Box A-6, Folder 13)
      Both prints have typescript leaves affixed to verso.
    - Apollo All Stars (Box A-6, Folder 14)
    - Apollo Contest Beauties (Box A-6, Folder 15)
    - Apollo Jan '86 Winners (Box A-6, Folder 16)
    - Apollo Models, The (Box A-6, Folder 17)
    - Apollo Theater (Box A-6, Folder 18)
      Folder title is "Apollo."
      Photographer if identified: Jeff Taylor
    - Apollo Theater (Box A-6, Folder 19)
      One print is stuck to the back of the folder. Another print has a typescript leaf and an ms. note attached with a paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Lem Peterkin, Bryan D. Hall, Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, David McAdams, Hairston Photo News Service, Bill Powell
    - Apollo Theater (Box A-6, Folder 20)
      One print is a Polaroid. Two prints are stapled together, one of which has a typescript leaf affixed to verso. Also contains one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Robert Brown
    - Apollo's 50th Anniversary (Box A-6, Folder 21)
    - Apollo's Amateur Night (1st after reopening) (Box A-6, Folder 22)
    - Aponte, Edward W. (Box A-6, Folder 23)
      Photographer if identified: Conrad Waldinger
    - Aponte, George (Box A-6, Folder 24)
      Print has staple in it.
      Photographer if identified: Ace Creative Photos
    - Aponte, Gladys (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 25)
    - Aponte, Irene (Box A-6, Folder 26)
    - Aponte-Quinones, Louis A. (Box A-6, Folder 27)
    - Apostolic Degrees of the Beulah Church (Box A-6, Folder 28)
    - Apple, Darwyn (Box A-6, Folder 29)
      Photographer if identified: Black Star
    - Applewhaite, Eleanor S. (Box A-6, Folder 30)
    - Applewhaite, Leon B. (Box A-6, Folder 31)
    - Applewhaite, Leon B. (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 32)
    - Appling, Jim (Box A-6, Folder 33)
    - Aquarium (Box A-6, Folder 34)
      Photo from the Seafloor Aquarium, Nassau, Bahamas
    - Arante, N. E. (Box A-6, Folder 35)
    - Araujo, John (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 36)
    - Araya, Zeuidi (Box A-6, Folder 37)
    - Arbona, Ramon (Box A-6, Folder 38)
    - Arbouin, Uvee Mdodana (Dr.) (Box A-6, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: Willis E. Allen, Hamilton Associates, Long Island Press Photographer's Assoc. (Cooper), Cecil Layne
    - ARC Gospel Singles (Box A-6, Folder 40)
    - Arcella, Franklin J. (Box A-6, Folder 41)
    - ARCH (Architecture Renewal Committee in Harlem) (Box A-6, Folder 42)
      One print has press release glued to verso.
    - Archbold, Phil C. (Box A-6, Folder 43)
    - Archbold, Tiny (Box A-6, Folder 44)
    - Archer, Andrew E. (Box A-6, Folder 45)
    - Archer, Cynthia (Box A-6, Folder 46)
    - Archer, Dennis W. (Box A-6, Folder 47)
    - Archer, Dudley (Dr.) (Box A-6, Folder 48)
    - Archer, Durward C. (Box A-6, Folder 49)
      One print has staple in it.
    - Archer, Edward (Box A-6, Folder 50)
    - Archer, Elsie (Box A-6, Folder 51)
    - Archer, Ernest L. (Box A-6, Folder 52)
    - Archer, Eva P. (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 53)
    - Archer, Gail P. (Box A-6, Folder 54)
      2 prints have staples.
    - Archer, Gail Palmore (Box A-6, Folder 55)
    - Archer, Glenn L. (Box A-6, Folder 56)
    - Archer, Henry H. (Box A-6, Folder 57)
      Photographer if identified: Photographic Unit NYC Transit Authority
    - Archer, James (Box A-6, Folder 58)
    - Archer, Jho (Box A-6, Folder 59)
    - Archer, Lee A. (Box A-6, Folder 60)
      Two velox prints. One print has staple in it.
      Photographer if identified: Norman Frederick, Everett Studios, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Archer, Lillian (Box A-6, Folder 61)
    - Archer, Mary (Box A-6, Folder 62)
    - Archer, Norman (Box A-6, Folder 63)
    - Archer, Sheila (Box A-6, Folder 64)
      Photographer if identified: Debbie Dobbelaer
    - Archibald, Edward (Box A-6, Folder 65)
    - Archibald, Elaine (Box A-6, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Ace Creative Photos
    - Archibald, Julius A. (Box A-6, Folder 67)
    - Archibald, Louis (Box A-6, Folder 68)
    - Archibald, Tiny (Box A-6, Folder 69)
    - Archibald, Warren (Box A-6, Folder 70)
      Photographer if identified: Jack A. Nedell
    - Architects, Future (Box A-6, Folder 71)
    - Ardelle, Toni (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 72)
      Print has photo caption stapled to it.
      Photographer if identified: Office of Communication United Church of Christ
    - Ardrey, William (Box A-6, Folder 73)
      Press release attached to print with paperclip.
    - Aremu, Aduke (Box A-6, Folder 74)
      One velox print. Press release attached to one print with paperclip. One print has staple in it.
      Photographer if identified: Leon Bolden
    - Aremu, Aduke (Box A-6, Folder 75)
    - Argent, Eugene (Box A-6, Folder 76)
    - Argrett, Joseph (Box A-6, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: Capitol and Glogau, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Arias, Juan (Box A-6, Folder 78)
    - Ariles, Carlos (Box A-6, Folder 79)
    - Arinze, Francis A. (Archbishop) (Box A-6, Folder 80)
      Photographer if identified: Barbeach Photographer
    - Arista (Box A-6, Folder 81)
    - Aristide (Box A-6, Folder 82)
      Photographer if identified: F. Leonidas
    - Aristide, Jean Bertrand (Box A-6, Folder 83)
      Photographer if identified: Joan Vitale Strong
    - Arkhurst, Frederick S. (Box A-6, Folder 84)
    - Arlen, Harold (Songbook) (Box A-6, Folder 85)
      Typescript leaf taped to verso of one print.
      Photographer if identified: Slade-Grossman
    - Armageddon (Box A-6, Folder 86)
    - Armand, Gesner (Box A-6, Folder 87)
      Photographer if identified: Joan McCullough
    - Armatrading, Joan (Box A-6, Folder 88)
    - Armatrading, Joan (Box A-6, Folder 89)
    - Armbrister, Samuel J. (Box A-6, Folder 90)
    - Armed Forces (Box A-6, Folder 91)
      Photographer if identified: Public Information Office Nassau County
    - Armendaris, Alex (Box A-6, Folder 92)
    - Armet, Marie (Box A-6, Folder 93)
    - Arms, Roderick (Box A-6, Folder 94)
    - Armstead, David (Box A-6, Folder 95)
    - Armstead, Dennis (Box A-6, Folder 96)
      Photographer if identified: Raymond Ross Photography
    - Armstead, Helen (Dr.) (Box A-6, Folder 97)
    - Armstead, James (Box A-6, Folder 98)
    - Armstrong, Alma (Box A-6, Folder 99)
      Photographer if identified: Ernie Pile
    - Armstrong, Almenia (Box A-6, Folder 100)
    - Armstrong, Bertrand (Box A-6, Folder 101)
    - Armstrong, Beverly (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 102)
    - Armstrong, Carlotta (Box A-6, Folder 103)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Mitchell, M Associates
    - Armstrong, Cecil Nathaniel (Box A-6, Folder 104)
    - Armstrong, Clifton (Box A-6, Folder 105)
    - Armstrong, Hobie (Box A-6, Folder 106)
    - Armstrong, James (Bishop) (Box A-6, Folder 107)
    - Armstrong, Jimmy (Box A-6, Folder 108)
    - Armstrong, Joe (Box A-6, Folder 109)
    - Armstrong, LaVerne (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 110)
    - Armstrong, Loretta (Box A-6, Folder 111)
    - Armstrong, Louis (Box A-6, Folder 112)
      Note on folder: "See inactive file."
    - Armstrong, Ninnie (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene/Creative Photo Service Inc.
    - Armstrong, Vanessa Bell (Box A-6, Folder 114)
    - Arnal, Issa (Box A-6, Folder 115)
    - Arnau, B. J. (Box A-6, Folder 116)
    - Arnau, Brenda (Box A-6, Folder 117)
    - Arneaud, Tony (Box A-6, Folder 118)
      Photographer if identified: Philip A. Demas
    - Arnett, Lawrence (Dr.) (Box A-6, Folder 119)
    - Arnette, Dorothy (Box A-6, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: Ciba-Geigy Corp. Photographic Department
    - Arno, A.V. (Rev.) (Box A-6, Folder 121)
    - Arnold, Haskell N. (Box A-6, Folder 122)
    - Arnold, Jimmy (Box A-6, Folder 123)
    - Arnold, Larkin (Box A-6, Folder 124)
    - Arnold, Valina (Box A-6, Folder 125)
    - Arpes, Brenda (Box A-6, Folder 126)
    - Arrendell, Inez R. (Box A-6, Folder 127)
    - Arricale, Frank (Box A-6, Folder 128)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Board of Education City of New York
    - Arrindell, Dan (Box A-6, Folder 129)
    - Arrindell, Helen (Box A-6, Folder 130)
      Print contains three images; a fourth has been clipped out.
    - Arrington, Alice (Box A-6, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons Foto, James Gilbert, Ross Photos
    - Arrington, Carl (Box A-6, Folder 132)
    - Arrington, Crawley J. (Box A-6, Folder 133)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Leon Henderson
    - Arrington, Darryl (Box A-6, Folder 134)
    - Arrington, Dick (Box A-6, Folder 135)
    - Arrington, Dorothy (Box A-6, Folder 136)
      Photographer if identified: Hamilton Associates
    - Arrington, Earl (Box A-6, Folder 137)
    - Arrington, Paulette Vernice (Box A-6, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Frank Silva
    - Arrington, Reginald (Box A-6, Folder 139)
    - Arrington, Richard (Box A-6, Folder 140)
      One magazine clipping.
      Photographer if identified: Arnold De Mille
    - Arrington, Roscoe A. (Box A-6, Folder 141)
    - Arrington, Sandra Ann (Box A-6, Folder 142)
      Photographer if identified: Scurlock
    - Arrington, Steve (Box A-6, Folder 143)
    - Arristin, Rosita (Box A-6, Folder 144)
    - Arrow (Box A-6, Folder 145)
      One print has staple in it, the other has press release stapled to verso.
    - Arrow Business Inst. (Box A-6, Folder 146)
      Photographer if identified: Patrick Owens
    - Arroyo, Carmen (Congresswoman) (Box A-6, Folder 147)
    - Arroyo, Marco A. (Box A-6, Folder 148)
      One velox print. One print is a Polaroid.
    - Arroyo, Martina (Box A-6, Folder 149)
      Fifteen prints have typescript leaves taped to verso. Of these, three have press releases attached with paperclip. Three more prints have press releases affixed with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Louis Melancon
    - Arroyo, Martina (Box A-6, Folder 150)
      Two prints have typescript leaves taped to verso. One print has typescript leaf stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Roddy McDowall
    - Arroyo, Tony (Box A-6, Folder 151)
      Photographer if identified: Troi Lancaster
    - Art (Box A-6, Folder 152)
      Six prints are stapled together.
      Photographer if identified: Geoffry Johnson, Peterkin Photo, Klytus
    - Art/Artists (Box A-6, Folder 153)
      Five prints mounted on sheet of construction paper. One print has ms. note and press release attached with paperclip. One print has staple in it. Also contains one art photocopy.
      Photographer if identified: Pam Link, Dawoud Bey, Pictorial Enterprise
    - ARC Gospel Choir, The (Box A-6, Folder 154)
    - Art Ensemble of Chicago (Box A-6, Folder 155)
    - Art, Rich (Box A-6, Folder 156)
      Blank sheet stapled to recto.
    - ARTC Community Choir (Box A-6, Folder 157)
    - Artenberg, A. C. "Gus" (Box A-6, Folder 158)
    - Arter Robert (Box A-6, Folder 159)
      One print has typescript leaf stapled to verso, and the other has typescript leaf stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: George Frye
    - Arthur, Alice (Box A-6, Folder 160)
    - Arthur, Alice (Box A-6, Folder 161)
    - Arthur, Anthony (Box A-6, Folder 162)
      Print is a Polaroid.
    - Arthur, Beatrice "Maude" (Box A-6, Folder 163)
      Print has typescript leaf formerly affixed to verso.
    - Arthur, Claris R. (Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 164)
      One print has three typescript leaves attached with paperclip.
    - Arthur, Harvin (Box A-6, Folder 165)
    - Arthur, Mae (Box A-6, Folder 166)
    - Arthur, Rudolph (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-6, Folder 167)
    - Arthur Barr Day Care Center (Box A-6, Folder 168)
    - Arthur's Round Table (Box A-6, Folder 169)
    - Artis, Bill (Box A-6, Folder 170)
    - Artis, Ruth (Box A-6, Folder 171)
      One print has ms. note taped to recto.
    - Artis, Stacey (Box A-6, Folder 172)
    - Artistics, The (Box A-6, Folder 173)
    - Artists, Harlem (Box A-6, Folder 174)
      Folder title is "Harlem Artist."
    - Artistry Beauty Salon (Box A-6, Folder 175)
    - Aruba (Box A-6, Folder 176)
    - Arum, Robert (Box A-6, Folder 177)